Girl you so fire
Ignited in my heart
내 심지에 On it
Spreading deep into my veins, burning up
혈관 깊이 퍼져 타올라
Gotta gotta get it
Yes I’m the KING
What you want? you got it.
Let me talk about it
Let me talk
The love that fills up every crevice of my body
내 뼛속까지 차오르는 Love
I wanna get it wanna get some more
This is what we came for came for
Now we gotta get our game on
Gotta shake the ground
Gonna break it down go
I’m afraid of the darkness
짙은 어둠이 두려워
Please light up my life
꺼진 내 불을 밝혀줘
I breathe in your love
난 네 사랑에 숨쉬어
Because that’s my world
그게 내 세상이니까
Here we go
Make it make it drop
Yeah my heart is like KING KONG
My heart goes pop pop
내 심장이 펑펑
Lose control
Never ever stop
Do it, Here we go
Bass drum
We go hard hard hard hard
Bass drum KING KONG
Feel a shock
느끼는 진동
Let’s go up to the top just like you want uh
네가 원한대로 올라 꼭짓점 uh
Let’s go together, we won’t die
함께 둘이 가자 죽지 않아
Don’t have to say it
굳이 발언 하지 말어
I don’t wanna wanna
wanna wanna wait!
Smash it, jump over it, leave it behind
부수고 뛰어넘고 제끼고
I don’t need anything else
필요 없어 너만 있음 만사 다 Okay
As long as I have you, everything’s okay
But don’t hold my baby responsible
But 내 Baby에게 책임을 물지마
Her only sin is making my heart beat
죄라면 단지 내 맘을 뛰게함
Makes my heart beat, I’m freaked out too
뛰게함 나도 식겁함
My heart which used to be like a stone
돌 같던 내 맘도
Shines like a pearl
진주 마냥 빛나더라
My heart keeps going Buh-ruh bum bum bum
심장은 쉴 새 없이 Buh-ruh bum bum bum
The love that fills up every crevice of my body
내 뼛속까지 차오르는 Love
You drive me crazy and I can’t control it
This is what we came for came for
Now we gotta get our game on
Gotta shake the ground
Gonna break it down go
I’m afraid of the darkness
짙은 어둠이 두려워
Please light up my life
꺼진 내 불을 밝혀줘
I breathe in your love
난 네 사랑에 숨쉬어
Because that’s my world
그게 내 세상이니까
Here we go
Make it make it drop
Yeah my heart is like KING KONG
My heart goes pop pop
내 심장이 펑펑
Lose control
Never ever stop
Do it, Here we go
Bass drum
We go hard hard hard hard
I’m holding (I’m waiting)
I’m running (I’m fading)
I’ll never give you up, not even for a minute,
널 끝까지 포기 못해 한순간 일분 일초까지
not even for a second
(I can be there)
I found you come to me
We’ll go to the top with you in my arms
널 품에 안고 올라
To a place where it’s just us two
우리 둘만 있는 곳으로
Get up get up move it
Get up get up rock your body
Put’em up Put’em up Hey
Hit me one more time
Get up get up move it
Get up get up rock your body
Put’em up Put’em up Put’em up
Like KING KONG